as you work through the course you'll be
required to download several files to
help you complete the assessments when
you download these files it's important
that you maintain an organizational
structure for the files so you can find
them easily and quickly the first thing
to do is hear a fiower folder and as you
can see I've already downloaded the for
assessment files I need to keep them
organized so what I like to do is put
them in a folder so what I need to do
here is create a folder and as I'm doing
an IT course and we'll give up the name
T course click away from it and that is
see if that name on the folder I can
then move the files by clicking or
holding
I'm just moving them across into the
folder if I now click on that folder I
can see all of the assessments are in
there in addition to this I would also
like to place each of the different
types of assessment into it - and
flawless I've got word processing
spreadsheets presentations and improving
productivity using IT so I need to
create a folder and I will call that one
WP - for word processing
well the word processing a suspect into
that folder now will then create a new
folder called up ps2 click away and I
can move that into the ps2 folder new
folder that's that's two and then move
that into the SS two folder and finally
and you fall before I can do two so now
I have the four units for the course
that you are going to complete when you
open up you can then click on your WP to
assessment which will open the fail that
will not in Word and once that is Robyn
you can begin your assessment so as you
work through your assessment you will
complete questions and tasks and do
various other activities in relation to
creating some documents you will enter
information in the here and the thing to
do there to make sure that you see
everything let's just click see if that
will automatically update the fail and
when you access it again it will have
the updated information